Gurkirat Kaur

Chandigarh, India

☐ 9461078872 • ☑ kaurgurkirat73@gmail.com in https://www.linkedin.com/in/gurkirat-kaur-2109-gs/

Profile Summary

I'm a young and enthusiastic student trying to have experience in all aspects of data. I can clean and organize datasets, query databases, manipulate data, and create reports or visualizations to present my findings. I possess a combination of technical expertise, analytical thinking, and a deep understanding of data, which allows me to unravel complex problems and make informed decisions.

Education

Chandigarh University

Computer Science, Statistics, Mathematics

Bachelor of Science - BSc

May 2021 - May 2024

"I was an obedient student having unwavering commitment to academic excellence and exemplary behaviour."

Blooming Dales International School

Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics

Apr 2020 - Jun 2021

Experience

Bharat Intern 1 month

Data Science Intern Oct 2023 - present

CodSoft 1 month

Data Scientist Sep 2023 - Oct 2023

Volunteering

Liason officer-2023: Cab meeting at Chandigarh University

Class Representative-2021: 12th at Blooming Dales International School

Projects

Project name: PCOS analysis

Sep 2023 - present Role-Data anaylst

Project description: Analyzing predictions on Polycystic ovary syndrome disease highly present in womens.

Project name: Titanic Survival Prediction

Role-Data scientist

1 week Aug 2023

Project description: In this project, you'll analyze the sales data of a retail store to help them better understand

their business performance. The goal is to provide insights that can improve decision-making.

Certifications

Foundations of project management: Google

Data Analytics: Google

Introduction to R: Great Learning **SQL for Data Science**: Great Learning

[&]quot;I was a confident speaker in school with strong leadership and problem-solving skills."

Python for Data Science: IBM

Everyday Excel: Coursera

Simulations: Virtual experience

Data Visualization: Tata Group

AutoML automated machine learning boot camp: Udemy

Skills

management skills: Event Planning, Cab meeting, project management

Microsoft Office: word, excel, powerpoint, ms access, outlook

Programming languages: c,c++,python,r programming,java,php,sas,sql

Data Visualization: power BI, tableau

Data Science: pandas,numpy,seaborn,scikit-learn,PyTorch,tensorflow,AWS

Abilities: Decision-making, teamwork

Extra-curricular Activities

Muskurahat Foundation

crowdfunding intern
serving needy people

Chandigarh University

Giddha team member Love to perform on stage

2 month

Sep 2023 - present

Nov 2021 - present